<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MusicApp</string>
    <string name="librairy">Library</string>
    <string name="playlist">Playlists</string>
    <string name="artists">Artists</string>
    <string name="albums">Albums</string>
    <string name="songs">Songs</string>
    <string name="artistName">Name of the artist</string>
    <string name="songName">Name of the song</string>
    <string name="play1">Playlist 1</string>
    <string name="play2">Playlist 2</string>
    <string name="play3">Playlist 3</string>
    <string name="art1">Artist 1</string>
    <string name="art2">Artist 2</string>
    <string name="art3">Artist 3</string>
    <string name="alb1">Album 1</string>
    <string name="alb2">Album 2</string>
    <string name="alb3">Album 3</string>
    <string name="song1">Song 1</string>
    <string name="song2">Song 2</string>
    <string name="song3">Song 3</string>
    <string name="addPlay">Add Playlist</string>

    <string name="nowPlayingDesc">This activity show and play the current
    song. There are buttons for moving to the next and previous songs in the playlist, one
        for a shuffled play and one that repeats the song. A seek bar shows the time position.
    One other seek bar for the volume of the song.</string>

    <string name="mainDesc">This activity is the summary to access to all activities. You can click on each
    part to access to a new activity. At the bottom, a little player showing the current song who is playing.
    4 buttons at this player, play, next, previous and expend to access to the PlayingActivity.</string>

    <string name="playlistDesc">This activity shows all playlists the user makes. In the future I will put
    a scrollview if there are too much playlist and change the TextView for a ListView of all playlists.
        I\'ll put buttons like play, edit, etc. He can also make a new playlist</string>

    <string name="artistDesc">This activity shows all artists. In the future if you click on one it will show
    all songs made by the artist. And you\'ll can play the songs of the artist.</string>

    <string name="albumDesc">This activity shows all albums. In the future if you click on one it will show
    all songs in the album. And you\'ll can play the songs of the artist.</string>

    <string name="songDesc">This activity shows all songs. In the future if you click on one will
        play the song.</string>

</resources>
